Charlotte Wesley Holloman Papers 140
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Charlotte Wesley Holloman Papers
1797-2013
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Holloman, Charlotte, 1922-2015
140
68 Boxes
Charlotte Wesley Holloman was an accomplished lyric soprano, classically-trained pianist and vocal teacher whose singing talents helped her establish a dynamic and internationally-acclaimed career. The Charlotte Wesley Holloman papers contain contains classical music scores, sheet music, recordings, newsclippings, correspondence, ephemera, art and artifacts, books, concert programs, vinyl LPs, and photographs.
Custodial History
Gift of Charlotte Holloman (daughter), 2016.
Biographical / Historical
Charlotte Wesley Holloman was an accomplished lyric soprano, classically-trained pianist and vocal teacher whose singing talents helped her establish a dynamic and internationally-acclaimed career. Holloman was born in Washington, D.C. to Florence Louise Johnson Wesley, a school teacher and Baltimore socialite, and Charles H. Wesley, well-known historian and minister. Holloman attended Miners Teachers College for her elementary school years. When her father was awarded a Guggenheim Fellowship, Holloman traveled with her parents and attended Regents Park Elementary School in London, England. After graduating from Dunbar High School in Washington. D.C. in 1937, Holloman entered Howard University and earned a bachelor's degree in music in 1941. Holloman also attended Columbia University, earning a master's degree in voice and music education in 1943. In the 1950s, Holloman appeared on Broadway, starring in "The Barrier," a musical about racial tensions based on Langston Hughes's work, and "My Darling Aida," a musical about a Southern plantation. Holloman was a featured soloist for recitals world-wide, including London and Berlin. She was a featured soloist for the Dayton Philharmonic, Boston Symphony, and Berkshire Music Festival at the height of her performance career. In 1961, Mrs. Holloman received the Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music grant to pursue voice studies with top instructors in Europe. She was contracted by the Saarbrücken and Essen opera companies in Germany, establishing a repertoire of 22 leading roles through her creation of major operatic characters in more than 13 operas in Germany, England and Italy. Once Holloman returned to the states, she began a dynamic career in higher education. She became an adjunct faculty member of the CUNY, Catholic University of America, Northern Virginia Community College, University of the District of Columbia, and Howard University. In addition to teaching and mentoring students at Howard University for over twenty years, Holloman maintained a private studio and provided vocal lessons up until her death in 2015.
Scope and Contents
The Charlotte Wesley Holloman papers contain contains classical music scores, sheet music, recordings, newsclippings, correspondence, ephemera, art and artifacts, books, concert programs, vinyl LPs, and photographs.
Women; African Americans; Music; Sheet music; Photographs; Ephemera; Correspondence; Education, higher; Performing Arts
- Series 1
  - Recordings/Albums, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Soprano Performance Program, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Town Hall Program, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - New York Herald Tribune, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Howard University Concert Series, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fire Routs Roland Hayes From Stage Article, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Gerald Alphenwaar Artists Representative Correspondence, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Cd-1750 Compact Disc Player Manual, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Pepsi Cola Company Audio Visual Aids, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chamber Music At The Library Of Congress Poster, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Schirmer'S Library Of Musical Classics, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Duetunes For Piano For Two Equal Players By Mary B. Merrill, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - The Children'S Own Book Of Folk Song, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - First Grade Piano Pieces, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Schirmer'S Library Of Musical Classics - Chopin, 1894 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - First Book Of Technical Studies By Elizabeth Quaile, 1925 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Concord Piano Books, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Michael Aaron Piano Course Grade 2, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Concored Duet Books, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Diller-Quaile Music Book, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - A Dozen A Day By Edna Mae-Burnam, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Caliph Of Bagdad By Bernice Benson Bentley, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Solo And Duet Books For The Piano, 1923 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - In Days Of Old: Ten Folk Tunes, 1923 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Easy Classics To Moderns, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Joh. Sebastian Bach, 1797 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Two Musical Impressions For The Piano By Jane Mattingly, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Hi-Lili, Hi-Lo: Simplified Piano Solo, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Tones And Overtones Spring 1955 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Frederic Chopin Works For The Pianoforte, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Brahms - Three Intermezzi, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Beethoven - Sonaten Music Book, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Beethoven Sheet Music, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Felix Mendelssohn, 1930s (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Back Choral Works, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Delta Sigma Theta Sorority Sheet Music, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Beatitudes Sheet Music, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Douglas Moore Sheet Music, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Douglas Moore Sheet Music, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Ernst Toch Sheet Music, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Great Songs Of The Sixties Sheet Music, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Unsorted Sheet Music, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Recordings/Albums, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Recordings/Albums, Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Cue Cards For Director'S Speeches, Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Black Cloth Personal University Black Book, Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Programs And Ads, 1949-1957 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, Letters, Correspondence, 1931-2010 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Clarice Smith Performing Arts Center 2006-2007 Season (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Holloman Apt. Copy (1 Of 2), Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Holloman Apt. Copy (2 Of 2), Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Charlottle Holloman Ad Cards, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Bulletins, 2002-2007 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Black History 2012 Discovery And Reflection (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Programs, Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings, Cards (1 Of 2), 1955-1957 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Programs, Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings, Cards (2 Of 2), 1954-1957 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Metropolitan Opera Forms And Correspondence, Undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Mini Photo Album, Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1954-1957 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Letters, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Bulletins, Newsletters, Magazines, 1967-1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Scrapbook - Newspaper Clippings And Correspondence (1 Of 2), 1953-1969 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbook - Newspaper Clippings And Correspondence (2 Of 2), 1953-1969 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Military Portrait, Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook: Newspaper Clippings, 1961-1965 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Evening Star - A New Star In Music'S Firmament, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Mmc Foundation Notes, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Prep For Wic '95 Notes, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Narrations For Hines-Lee Spring Concert, Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Opera And Recital Criticisms And Biography, Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Holloman'S Biographies, Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Charlotte Wesley Holloman Biography And Cv, Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Memoribilia, Cards, Photographs, 2009-2014 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Performance Programs, 2009-2014 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Photograph, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Jet Magazine, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Book Of Performance Ads, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Holloman Newspaper Ads, 1941-1961 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Howard University Bulletin, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Howard University Charter Day Observance, Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Experimental Program In Thematic Studies, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Holloman Photograph Film, Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Concert Ads And Criticisms, 1956-1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Commission On The Arts And Humanities, 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Licenses, Teaching Contracts, Transcripts, 1943-1970 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Teaching File, Employment File, Letters Of Recommendation, Etc., 1970-1987 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Autograph Books, Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Award From Junior High School, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - National Visionary Leadership Project And Biographical Information, 1954-2010 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - First New York Recital Ad And Second Convo Appearance, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Repetoire, 1950-1993 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - 2011 Appointment Book (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 2009 Appointment Book (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - 2008 Appointment Book (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Photo Album, Undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - 1999 Appointment Book (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - 2013 Appointment Book (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - 2006 Appointment Book (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Happy Birthday And Thank You Notes, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Guest Book, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 2007 Appointment Books (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Europe - Your Custom-Planned Itinerary, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Cv, Biography, Repetoire, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Auditioning In Europe, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Washington International Competition Notes, Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Hines-Lee Opera Ensemble, 1992-2004 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Dawn Magazine, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2009 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Biographies And Interview Transcripts, Undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Howard Employment, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - George Shirley, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Performance Ads, Flyers, And Programs, 2009-2012 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Photographs, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Roll Book, Undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Newsletter - St. Philip'S Church, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Performing Arts Ads, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Blacks In Classical Music - A Personal History By Raoul Abdul, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1965-2012 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Cv, Undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Programs, 1953-1963 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Student Schedule 2014 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence (1 Of 2), 1950-2004 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence (2 Of 2), 1953-1963 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Agreements And Contracts, 1953-1956 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Department Of Health And Physical Examination, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Flight Information, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Newsletter - Paul Laurence Dunbar, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Negro History Bulletin, 19815 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - 2005 Appointment Book (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Howard University, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Kennedy Center Jazz, Undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Porgy And Bess, Undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Notes From Duncan'S Studio, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Opera And Recital Criticism, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Focus On Lehman College, Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Black Enterprise, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Afro American Newspaper, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Opera Department Auditions Paperwork, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Brooks United States Senator, Undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1968-2007 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Department Of Motor Vehicles Info, 2014 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Musical Toronto - Issachah Savage, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Biographies, 2009-2013 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Vocal Arts Society, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Howard University Faculty Information, 2010-2013 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Programs, Performance Ads, Certificates (1 Of 2), 1950-2004 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Programs, Performance Ads, Certificates (2 Of 2), 1950-2004 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Newspapers, 1993-2000 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Manhattan United Church Women May Fellowship Luncheon, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Black American Choral Song And Music Of The Black American Composer, 1984-1988 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - United States Army Chorus, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1976-2009 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Articles, 1954-1991 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Programs, Certificates, Ads, 1956-2009 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Black History 2012 Discovery And Reflection, Undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - John L.S. Holloman Memorial, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Wilma Shakesnider, Undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - 2010 Appointment Book (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Press Book For Todd Duncan, Undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Letters To Charlotte'S Parents Sent From Europe, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Resumes, Biographies, Cvs, Undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Written Music And First Music Writing Book, Undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Class Record Book, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Date Book, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Music Programs, Class Info, Ads, Service Awards, 1994-2012 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Friday Morning Music Club, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Charles Sumner Museum, Archives And Gallery, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Baltimore Summer Opera Workshop, 2010-2011 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Department Of Veterans Affairs, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Todd Duncan Newspaper Clippings, 1944-2003 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Todd Duncan Notes, 1943-1995 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Todd Duncan Photographs, Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Handwritten, Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Reviews, Programs, Criticisms, 2009-2012 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1961-2002 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Howard University College Of Arts And Sciences, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Musical Courier, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Charles H. Wesley Bio, Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Henderson Papers Collection, Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - In Memory Of Dr. Hortense Reid Kerr And List Of Spirituals, Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Vocal Scores, Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - A Name To Remember By Pearl Boatwright, Undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Etudes De Solfege, Undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Certificate Of Appreciation - Central State College, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Stetcher And Horowitz Piano Library, Undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Art Wire, Undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Remarks By Dr. Rae Alexander-Minter, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Paul Robeson - Here I Stand, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Conversation With George Shirley, Undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - George Walker Sheet Music, 1971-1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Burleigh-Spiritual, 1917-1969 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Ai-45599-01, Undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - The Green Pastures, Spirituals, Arranged For Voice And Piano, By Hall Johnson, Undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript - Howard Swanson, Undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Sheet Music, Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Thomas Kerr, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Negro Art Songs, Undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Lillian Evanti, Undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Spirituals - Black Composers, 1931-1940 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Play Songs Of The Deep South, Undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - 24 Negro Melodies, Undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - My Songs, African American Religious Folk Songs, Arranged And Interpreted, Undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Hall Johnson, Undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - S Coleridge Taylor, Undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Requiem For Four Solo Voices And Chorus, Undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Old American Songs; Second Set, Undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Five Songs Of Laurence Hope, Undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Poeme D'Hiver, Undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Modern Soprano Operatic Album, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - G. Schirmer'S Collection Of Masses And Vespers, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Operatic Repertoire, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Verdi Rigolette, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Brahms. 70 Songs For Voice And Piano, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Celebrated Open Arias, Undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Strauss. 30 Songs For Voice And Piano, Undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Mozart Requiem, Undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Operatic Anthology, Undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Operatic Anthology, Undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Puccini. Tosca, Undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - J.S. Bach Choral Works, Undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Franz Schubert, Undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - The Messiah, Undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Rossini - Serate Musicali, Undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Operatic Anthology, Undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Bizet - Carmen, Undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Black Magic, Lanston Hughes And Milton Meltzer, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Photographs And Clippings Of Charlotte, 1947-1970 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - May Pageant, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Advertisement, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, 1930-1960 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1930-1960 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Pagent And Recital, 1930-1960 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Guestbook, Undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Hall Johnson Collection, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Recital Notes, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Sheet Music, Undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Sheet Music (Mostly Popular), Undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Sheet Music (Mostly Popular), Undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Tristan Und Isolde 1906 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Puccini Die Boheme 1897 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Rastlose Liebe, Restless Love 1951 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Faure, Twenty-Five Selected Songs for High Voice 1946 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - A Treasury of Grand Opera 1946 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Vanessa, Samuel Barber 1957 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - La Flora Volume Primo 1949 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Belcanto, 10 Ancient Italian Arias undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Contemporary Songs in English undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Franz Liszt, Thirty Songs undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Art Songs for School and Studio undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Personnages, 1954-2001 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Hansel and Gretel undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Henry Purcel ,The Fairy Queen Opera undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Die Meistersinger Von Nurnberg Richard Wagner undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Turandot undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - In Halt undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Mozart Cosi Fan Tutte undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - G. Schirmer's Collection of Song and Duet Albums undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Verdi Rigoletto undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Don Giovanni Mozart undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - A. Carlos Gomez, Colombo 1892 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Giacomo Puccini, Madame Butterfly undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Schumann Duette undated (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Mahler 24 Songs for Voie and Piano and Schumann, Woman's Life and Love undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Fifty Mastersongs by Twenty Composers, Undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Arien- Album Sopran, Undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Carmen Score, Undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - La Traviata, Vocal Score, Undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Meinen Lieben Verwandten, der Familie Pschorr in Munchen, Undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Herod, The Play of A Twelfth Century Musical Drama, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - The Old Maid and the Thief by Gion Carlo Menotti 1943 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Franz Schubert Songs, Undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Care Selve, Come Beloved Arranged by A.L, Undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Cantata, Alessandro Scarlatti, Undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Et Retablo de Maese Pedro, Undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Julia Culp - Mezzo, Low Key, Undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - The International Library of Music, Undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Song Contents by Type, Undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Great Art Sons of Three Centuries, Undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Still Wie Die Nacht, Silent as Night, Undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - You Can Tell the World, Negro Folk Song, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Letters, from the Opera Werther, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Cesar Franck Symphony, Undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Upper Room Hymns, Undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - G. Schirmer's Collection of Oratorios and Catatas, Undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Tosca, Undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - The Bohemians, Undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - The Prodigal Son, Undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Elijah, An Oratorio, Undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Out of Darkness, Undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Maytime, Undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Songs you Like to Sing, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Bethlehem, Undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Hanzel and Gretel, Undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Pelleas et Melisande, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Chanson Populaires, 1910 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Vocalizzi, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Mein Singendes Klingendes Wien, Undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - A Treasury of Stephen Foster, Undated (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Igor Stawinsky le Rossignol, Undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Daphne von Richard Strauss, Undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - The Modern Soprano, Undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Dalbert Tiefland, Undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Parte Terza, Undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Anthology of Sacred Song, Celebrated Arias Selected from Oratorios, Undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Virgil Thomson, Four Saints in Three Acts, Undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - The Crucifixion, Undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Ricci Varizoni - Cadenze Tradizioni, 1903 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Ariadne Auf Naros, Richard Strauss, Undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Fifty Songs, Robert Franz, Undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Fifty Songs, Edward Grieg, Undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Jensen, Undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Classic Songs, Italian/French/English, Undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - American Arias for Soprano, Undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Winter Words, Benjamin Britten, Undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Richard Wagner, Tristan und Isolde, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Debussy 43 Songs for Voice and Piano, Undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Faure Twenty Five Selected Songs for High Voice, Undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Ludwig Van Beethoven Prometheus, Undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Operatic Anthology, celebrated arias, Undated (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Werther, an opera in folk arts, "letters", Undated (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - The Family Music Book, Undated (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Sheet music, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - 40 French Songs, For Voice and Piano, Undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Henry Purcell, Die Nacht, Undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Henry Purcell, Songs with Realizations of the Figured Bass, Undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Schirmer's Collection of Opera's Aida, 1925 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Jaques Offenbach, 1911 (Box 31, Folder 5)